Pretty. Awkward.
No Hard Feelings is a comedy, romance film directed by Gene Stupnitsky.
On the brink of losing her childhood home, Maddie discovers an intriguing job listing: wealthy helicopter parents
looking for someone to “date” their introverted 19-year-old son, Percy, before he leaves for college.
To her surprise, Maddie soon discovers the awkward Percy is no sure thing.
Maddie Barker, played by Jennifer Lawrence.
Percy Becker, played by Andrew Barth Feldman.
Allison Becker, played by Laura Benanti.
Sara, played by Natalie Morales.
Laird Becker, played by Matthew Broderick.
Jim, played by Scott MacArthur.
No Hard Feelings is a 2023 American sex comedy film starring Jennifer Lawrence as a woman hired by a wealthy
couple to romance their romantically and sexually inexperienced son, played by Andrew Barth Feldman.
The film is directed by Gene Stupnitsky from a
screenplay he co-wrote with John Phillips.
Along with Lawrence—who was one of the film's producers—and Feldman, the film
stars Laura Benanti, Natalie Morales, and Matthew Broderick.
The project was announced in October 2021, when Sony Pictures Releasing and Columbia Pictures
won a bidding war between Apple Original Films, Netflix and Universal Pictures.
Lawrence joined the cast and produced the film with
Stupnitsky attached to direct it.
Much of the cast joined in September to October 2022.
Filming began in late September in various Nassau County locations in the
New York City metropolitan area and finished in November.
No Hard Feelings was theatrically released in the United States
on June 23, 2023, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
It received positive reviews from critics and grossed over $87
million worldwide against a $45 million budget.
Lawrence earned a nomination for Best Actress in a Motion Picture – Comedy or Musical at the 81st Golden Globe
Awards, and won the Comedy Movie Star of the Year award at the 49th People's Choice Awards.
The film was nominated for Best Comedy at the 29th Critics' Choice Awards.
The film explores themes of friendship, older woman seduces
younger guy, romcom, summer, new york state.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.